A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Corporation, Biography FA872
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Correspondence and Biography, 1901-1971
  - Welch, William Henry, 1850-1934 (1901-1933), 2 folders, 2 volumes (Box 6)
    - Simon, Flexner. William Henry Welch and the heroic age of medicine by Simon Flexner and James Thomas Flexner. New York, Viking Press, 1941, 1 volume. (Box 6)
      Removed to the RAC Library, 8/9/98.
    - Flexner, Simon. William Henry Welch, a biographical sketch, 1 volume. (Box 6)
      Removed to RAC Library 8/9/98.
    - Introduction from Papers and Addresses by William Henry Welch, 1920. Vol. 1, xi-xxxiv (Box 6)
    - Pamphlet: The Eightieth Birthday of William Henry Welch (Box 6)
    - Flexner, S. Doctor William H. Welch. 1850-1934 Science 79 (1934) 529-53 (Box 6)